From the Library of Congress
in Washington, DC.
I'm Simon Bar Sinister,
Sailor so Hardy and Hail.
I live on an island
on the back of a whale.
It's a whale of an island.
That's not a bad joke.
Its lord and its master
is this handsome bloke.
Ooh, the most remarkable
extraordinary fellow.
Oh,
sing about the Salem.
I scare all creation on land or on sea.
But talk about women,
they all fall for me.
I take my adventures
wherever they're found.
I don't want to brag, folks.
But I've been around.
Who's the most phenomenal,
extra special kind of fellow?
Centipede the salamander.
From the Valley of Serpents,
these diamonds I took.
I clean out those serpents
with one dirty look.
Ha ha.
Serpents.
Look at this monster
so strong and so huge.
He'd frightened King Kong,
but he's only my student.
The capture of Mula for me was just fun.
Whoever said two heads
were better than one,
ha ha.
All the most phenomenal,
extraordinary fellow.
Huge, Sinlauzi, the sailor.
On one of my travels, I ran into this.
Now, there was a thrill
I'd be sorry to miss.
He spread out his wings
and the sunlight grew dim.
He took me in his beak,
But I ran off with him.
Oh, the most remarkable
extraordinary fellow.
Sinbad the Sailor.
The most phenomenal extra
special kind of fellow.
Sinbad the Sailor.
I'm afraid of nobody under the sun.
All I say is, Boom!
I'm one of the most remarkable
extra ordinary fellows.
It's poppy the sailor man.
I'm one of the sailor men.
I'm strong to the finish 'cause I eat
my spinach and I'm poppy the sailor man.
I'm one tough gazorka which hates all
polkas but hates on the up and square.
White biffs and I buffs them and always
have Rough 'em, but none of them gets
nowhere if anyone dares to risk me first,
it's pop and it's wham, understand?
So keep good behavior, that's your one
life saver with by the sail, a man.
Pop by the sail, a man.
I'm strong to the finish, 'cause I eats me
spinach, I'm pop by the swaiway, the man.
Who thought the air was not so
sour and dares to challenge Zinbad?
I have a fission.
Ripped that ship.
But bring me the woman.
Oh, oh!
Oh, what happened?
Oh, oh, let me go, let me go, let me go!
No, no, no, don't let me go,
don't- oh, man, the lifeboats are gone.
Oh, that was a nice ship we had once.
Hey, did you see the same thing I saw?
I'm gonna take another look
at that thing, see what there was.
That's the biggest buzzard I ever saw.
Look at the size of that thing.
Oh, where am I?
Hey, keep away from me, you!
Stop that!
Leave me alone!
I won't do that!
I'll come here!
I won't!
Get up, sugar, and give us a little smack.
I'll give you a smack all
right, all right there!
Hey, we gotta save olive oil.
Come on, Wimpy, hurry
up before it's too late.
Into the drink.
Into the line, everybody up.
What's this?
The Isle of Sodor and enter not
for soothsayer passeth it passeth us.
The soothsayer.
Luncheon.
Here I go with it.
I don't like this place at all.
Sorry I ever came in here.
It's kind of spooky to me.
Oh, yeah.
Try to scare me like
that, huh?
Can you imagine nothing down my nose
trying to scare me like that?
Help, Papa!
Save me!
Oh, I'm coming out of.
I just got a little wall here.
Do I have footprints or something?
Oh.
Oh, I wanna stop.
I wanna stop this dancing.
Stop.
Well, you have invited me.
Come on.
Who invited you?
I did.
What are you gonna do about it, huh?
How did you get in here?
Oh, oh, fouled again.
I must resort to my last hamburger.
Oh.
Oh, huh?
Hey, I wants me goil.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Who are you?
I'm Pop by the Sail, a man.
Who am I?
You heard what I said.
That's what I said.
Why?
Who's the most remarkable,
extraordinary fellow?
Yo!
I just wanna punch you in the face.
Who's the most phenomenal,
extra special kind of fellow?
Yo!
I'm all made of nobody under the sun.
All I say is boo and my enemies run.
Who's the most remarkable,
extraordinary fellow?
Who?
Popeye the sailor.
What?
You better fix your shirt
there, young fellas.
Hey, hey.
Well, let's see how great you are.
Hey, let's sit down.
You may.
Oh, what's this?
Hey, let me down, you big older bro.
What are you doing?
Take me for a ride or something?
Hey.
Oh,
I'm going to sleep.
My baby kid, my peaches
and cream, my baby kid.
If you don't sleep, my baby kid,
I close for you your two eyes like this.
Oh, two against one, huh?
How do you like that?
What for you like
that Popeye smacker face?
How do you like about that?
You hold that Popeye in this hand.
By Carbonite, if I had that mug in this
hand, I make from him special
dish of chopped fritocises.
I don't like chopped fritocises.
I made for you to like it.
Oh, why you two-headed
face for Yonf Fiction?
How do you like that?
Ooh.
Come on, you're gonna take
a double dose of this.
Well, I guess I fixed those two fellas.
I won't hear for them.
Oh, yeah.
Who's gonna make who like chicken?
There's only room for one
great sailor in this world.
That's me.
Oh, meat for meat kiddo,
that's what I gotta say.
Oh,
meat for meat kiddo,
that's what I gotta say.
Make a boo.
I saw you.
Don't leave me now.
Oh.
Come on, get up on the bike.
Give it to him, Popeye.
Give him the Twisker Punch.
Twisker Punch coming up.
Take that.
This has been a presentation
of the Library of Congress.
Visit us at loc.
gov.