From the Library of Congress
in Washington, D.C.
I'm telling you, it's going to be some
trouble in this game here in a minute.
Yeah, I got to be prepared.
Kill a goat.
No, go ahead, excuse me.
Say, man, man, look at y'all.
Brother, y'all can't be shooting these
dices down here in the chair,
flow like this, yeah?
Smart fella.
Do you know who I am?
No.
I have the jurisdiction here
at this place, that's what I am.
Yeah, who's running this game?
I'm running the game.
Well, look here, that white man has
paid me to keep this place clean here.
But look like you trying to clean me here.
That's all right, you go ahead and play,
but you know, look out for me.
Yeah, but don't come
around too regular now.
I'm gonna call on you again.
What y'all say?
Give me a chance.
Hey, Jimmy, did you see your old lady?
You know I seen your old lady.
You seen me with this money,
I ain't working no more.
Look here, Jimmy, give me a bet, will you?
Oh, man, let me get in the game for you.
All right, boys,
shoot that five of the nickel there.
Let them go then.
What do you want?
Let them go.
Hell, baby, no honey was everything.
Wait a minute, I'm trying
to make me some money here.
Yeah.
What you doing with the day?
That's all right.
What is it?
Seven, you see what it is?
No, I thought I'd do that.
No.
What you gonna do, Jimmy?
I'm gonna shoot two or three dollars.
All right, that's all right.
The more you don't pay, the more you
don't pay, and they'll put it down.
Yeah, yeah.
Get it out of your hand.
That's all you got.
Hey, Jimmy, come on, give me the bit.
Why you gonna let a man stand
there and take the day's work?
Not the way, son.
Don't be bothering now.
Yeah, Jimmy, go ahead
and give me the bite, baby.
Let me give it some air.
I hope you do, I show you,
'cause I need every pound of it.
Now I'm gonna try here.
I'm gonna bet it on now, every
pound get the fat ass.
Get down on it.
Yeah, it is.
Let's go.
Look out, there.
What kind of woman is that?
You are, that's a pretty yellow woman.
You know they love to do anything.
You never get to do what
a yellow woman want to do.
Mm-.
Well, well, well, come on, sweetheart.
I didn't know you was that lucky.
How long has he been
butting with that door?
Oh, man, he been going for a long time.
Say, Jimmy, wait, I forgot to ask you.
Give me a bit, boy.
Yeah, come on, get broke, I can't
get a quarter from no one.
Give me a bit, boy.
Come on, get up off that thing.
Well, now, wait a minute,
the man don't shoot the pistol.
What's the matter, you're chewing me?
Man's just leaving me my cut.
Maybe close that door,
there's some gin over there.
Okay, baby.
Now, look here, honey,
what did you do with them dollars?
Was nothing to it, baby.
Stick with me and you'll
always have money.
Well, I don't know what you did when you
was behind my back, but whatever
you did, it was tank like that.
Now listen here, Jimmy.
What would you do now
if Bethy walked in here?
Oh, honey, don't pay Bethy no mind.
Don't pay Bethy no mind.
No, this is my room.
Bethy just pays for it.
Oh yeah.
Come here, baby.
You old sweet devil, you.
You know, honey, I sure like you.
I like you too, honey.
This is my off day.
Well, get some more money and come back.
Oh, what are you talking about?
See you again, fella.
See you, Emmy.
Come on, Emmy.
Look here, why does Jimmy
carry that yellow woman?
In Bessie's room.
Where?
In Bessie's room, you know where.
Hey, what is all that talk going
on around here about Bessie?
Ma, ma, I don't know what
you're talking about.
Hey, what's wrong?
Go to your room, honey.
What?
Don't look at me, I told you not
to come up here in the first place.
Well, I guess I'll be going now.
Not yet.
You got to see me before you go.
You little rascal,
you ought to be coming in my room.
Hey, Jimmy, get this woman off of me.
I can't do you no good, honey.
Dad, what are you doing with this woman?
Yeah, y'all can't raise
all this sand in here.
What's the matter with you?
What's the trouble with you?
Well, look here, I'm the gentleman, I
don't want-- I don't care who you is,
I don't care if you're the landlord, you
ain't got nothing to do in my business.
You gonna move?
I don't care.
Let me move.
You're gonna move.
Do not pay my rent.
Come on out.
You're gonna move.
Don't you hear me?
Now, yeah.
Now, wait a minute.
Just grab the woman.
Jimmy, don't leave me.
Jimmy, please don't leave your best.
Jimmy, you ain't gonna leave me are you?
Woman, I'll be gone before
the evening sun goes down.
Jimmy, don't I give you
everything you say you want?
What have I got?
I give you clothes, clothes.
I give you suits, suits, yeah,
singular baby, not plural,
one suit, that's all, one suit.
Don't leave me, Jimmy.
A woman, get out of my face.
Don't leave, Jimmy, please.
Don't leave, Jimmy.
My man
My man's got a heart like a rock
In the sea, my man's got a heart
like a rocket in the sea.
My man's got a heart
Like a rocket, I do see
That evening, I
ain't seen that evening,
I ain't seen that evening, I ain't seen